{
  "LevelId": 7,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 59,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "SYSTEM",
      "question": "Network of components working together"
    },
    {
      "id": 60,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "ARREST",
      "question": "legal process of taking someone into custody due to suspicion of a crime"
    },
    {
      "id": 61,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "BULLET",
      "question": "small, metal projectile fired from a gun"
    },
    {
      "id": 62,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "SAFETY",
      "question": "describes measures taken to prevent accidents or harm"
    },
    {
      "id": 63,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "BUMPER",
      "question": "Car's impact absorber"
    },
    {
      "id": 64,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "BOTHER",
      "question": "Annoy or trouble"
    },
    {
      "id": 65,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "RESORT",
      "question": "people often go for relaxation and vacation"
    },
    {
      "id": 66,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "CORNER",
      "question": "meeting point of two converging lines or the edge of a surface where it turns"
    },
    {
      "id": 67,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "DEFECT",
      "question": "flaw or imperfection in something"
    },
    {
      "id": 68,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "TELEPHONE",
      "question": "Communication device with a dial or keypad"
    }
  ]
}